## Nicolas Kirsch

#### 0852813871

www.linkedin.com/in/nicolas-kirsch-nicok8811@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

My name is Nicolas Kirsch, I have been working in Customer Service and Sales for 8 years. Including a global company, an international company, and an organization with more than 100 branches with national deployment. Always achieving corporate objectives, respecting the ideals of the company. My skills include sales, research and development of sales opportunities, digital content creation, excellent computer and oral communication skills with clients and colleagues. My goal is to stand out as a marketer, creating strategies and content, always looking for progress, to be promoted.

## Skills

#### Organization skills, able to multi-task, with strong attention to detail.

- In charge of many activities at the same time, individually or in groups, completed in time and form. Great stress management.

#### **Design and Content Creation**

- Management of Adobe Premiere and Photoshop, creation of flyers and Videos. Management of social networks such as Facebook, |Instagram, Twitter. Creation of relevant content to attract and retain customers.

#### **Brainstorming and Develop Marketing Opportunities**

-8 years of sales experience. Winner of National Sale Contest for Sony Centre. Great Lead Generator and great listening skills. Understanding and understanding personalization in sales strategy.

#### Leadership

Inspiring, great communicator, self-training in Emotional Intelligence. Motivational techniques. Excellent group communication

#### **Education**

- Independent Colleges BA(Honours) in Marketing. Level 8 Second year. (Dublin, Ireland) <u>Currently Studying</u>
- eCollege.ie Adobe Photoshop Course (Official) Virtual Design (2021)
- Eric Levy School, Dublin Barista certificate (2020)
- Future Proof Training, Dublin Manual Handling and HACCP (2020)
- **Cetear Technology (College)** Rosario, Professional Musician. 2005-2009 (Graduated) Producing, recording, mixing and mastering music.

## Work Experience

### The Castle Hotel – (Breakfast Receptionist) (2022 – 2023)

- Excellent reception of guests and designation of tables
- Maintenance of services offered at breakfast.
- Waitress
- Make coffee and smoothies.

## Koffee and Kale – (Barista, Waitress, Cashier) (2022) Dublin

- Responsible for making different kind of coffees.
- Cash management and great sale of all products
- Order products from supplier
- Opening and closing of the premises

#### Alfie's Restaurant - (Receptionist) (2020-2022) Dublin

Customer Reception.

## Musimundo, (Salesman)- 11 2017- 10 2019 Rosario, Argentina

#### **Electronic Retail Store**

- I sold electronic items of varied brands like Samsung, Sony. Such as sound equipment, household appliances, as well as personal loans.
- Number one salesperson on the team, and I won several prizes for achieving sales quotas.
- Managed a monthly spreadsheet for analysing sales.
- Sony Centre, (Salesman). 11 2016-10 2017 Rosario, Argentina Flagship Sony Store in Rosario. Argentina.
- I received a significant amount of training for this job, which helped me to sell a wide variety of high-tech equipment and devices.
- Top salesperson in the country for the PlayStation 4.
- I was proud to work for a top company and worked hard to reach sales targets.

# **Foxtrot Music Centre Record Shop**, Sales Assistant: Rosario - Argentina. - 2012 - 2016

- The number one record shop in the city. I oversaw having specific orders imported from all over the world.
- Responsible for end of day procedures such as closing the shop and balancing the tills.